A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Attorney General, 1988 - 1997.
Library of Virginia
- Speeches, 1988-1997. (Box 1-4)
  - Political Speeches, 1992-1997. (Box 2-3)
    - Alexandria Republican City Committee, 1995 Dec 11. (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Bliley Breakfast, 1995 Dec 18. (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Speech Log, 1996-1997. (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - GOP Courts of Justice Governor's Breakfast, 1996 Jan 18. (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - FOP Legislative Rally, 1996 Jan 24. (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Republican Advance Invocation, 1996 Jan 26. (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Republican Advance - Dinner, 1996 Jan 26. (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - GOP Advance - State Central Committee, 1996 Jan 27. (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Lincoln Dinner, 1996 Feb 10. (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Peninsula Lincoln Day Dinner, 1996 Feb 22. (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Washington County Lincoln Day, 1996 Feb 24. (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Pat Mullins Roast, 1996 Mar 15. (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - AG's Dinner, 1996 Apr 2. (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Randy Forbes Reception, 1996 Apr 12. (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Southwest Virginia Tours, 1996 Apr 22. (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - VFRM Conference, 1996 Apr 27. (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Armenian Martyrs Day, 1996 Apr 28. (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Suffolk Prayer Breakfast, 1996 May 2. (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Shrimp Festival, 1996 May 10. (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - District Conventions, 1996 May 11. (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - WRVA Interview, 1996 May 13. (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - 13th Annual Convention and Education Fair, 1996 May 14. (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Wiley, Rein, and Fielding Luncheon, 1996 May 24. (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - GOP Convention, 1996 May 31. (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Republican State Convention, 1996 June 1. (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Baptist General Convention, 1996 June 25. (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Lynchburg Domestic Violence Conference, 1996 June 27. (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - WRVA, 1996 July 1. (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Masons, 1996 Sept 24. (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Charlottesville-Albemarle Business, 1996 Nov 18. (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Staunton-Augusta Business, 1996 Nov 18. (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Advance-Roanoke, 1996 Dec 5. (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - VFRW, 1997 Jan 9. (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Concerned Women of America, 1997 Jan 20. (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - FOP Rally Day, 1997 Jan 22. (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Family Foundation, 1997 Feb 7. (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Suffolk-Nansemond NAACP, 1997 Feb 8. (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Jewish Community, 1997 Feb 10. (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Richmond Academy of Medicine, 1997 Feb 11. (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Blue Ribbon Commission, 1997 Feb 13. (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Central Virginia Financial Executives, 1997 Feb 18. (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Lawyers for Gilmore, 1997 Feb 19. (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Peninsula Lincoln Day Dinner, 1997 Feb 20. (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Trigon Check Presentation, 1997 Feb 21. (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - ATLA/Regent University School of Law, 1997 Mar 3. (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Charlottesville FOP, 1997 Mar 10. (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Financial Planners, 1997 Mar 14. (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - National Triad Conference, 1997 Mar 17. (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - International Trade Luncheon, 1997 Mar 28. (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - VFRW Convention, 1997 Apr 18. (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Stafford Rotary Club, 1997 Apr 9. (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Northern Neck Chamber of Commerce, 1997 Apr 16. (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Victims Rights Luncheon, 1997 Apr 15. (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Ducks Unlimited, 1997 Apr 18. (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Rotary International, 1997 Apr 18. (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Virginia Horse Festival, 1997 Apr 19. (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Victims Rights Week Ceremony, 1997 Apr 19. (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Association of General Contractors, 1997 May 13. (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - I-66 Prince William Partnership, 1997 May 22. (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Virginia Technology Summit, 1997 May 21. (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Economic Developers Association, 1997 Sept. (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Transportation, 1997 Sept 19. (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Hampton Roads Chamber of Commerce, 1997 Dec 11. (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Miscellaneous Speeches, 1988-1992. (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1988-1989. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990-1992. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Scheduling, 1996-1997. (Box 4-5)
  - Event Files, 1996-1997. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Bar Association, 1996 July 19. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Youth Alcohol and Drug Abuse Prevention Project, 1996 July 23. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Family Violence Commission, 1996 July 24. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Commonwealth Attornies, 1996 Aug 1. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Pro-Am Fishing, 1996 Aug 3. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Church Rally, 1996 Aug 4. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Violence Prevention Institute, 1996 Aug 6. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Fraternal Order of Police, 1996 Aug 8. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Williams, Mullen, Christian and Dobbins, 1996 Aug 26. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Church Building Conference, 1996 Aug 27. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Electric Car, 1996 Sept 5. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Faberg Ball, 1996 Sept 7. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - BMG Metals, 1996 Sept 9. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Sheriff's Association, 1996 Sept 10. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Attorney General's Schedule, 1996 Sept 11. (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Assembly of Independent Baptists, 1996 Sept 20. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - School Superintendents, 1996 Sept 20. (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Wolf Trap Ball, 1996 Sept 20. (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Hanes 500 Race, 1996 Sept 22. (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Masonic Lodge, 1996 Sept 24. (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Covington and Burling, 1996 Sept 30. (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Commonwealth Day, 1996 Oct 1. (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Family Violence Prevention, 1996 Oct 7. (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Governor's Forum on Crime, 1996 Oct 15. (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Virginia Association of School Superintendents, 1996 Oct 17. (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - William and Mary School of Law Symposium, 1996 Oct 17. (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Hampton Roads Chamber of Commerce, 1996 Oct 18. (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Virginia Conference on World Trade, 1996 Oct 21. (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Virginia Automobile Dealers, 1996 Oct 24. (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Domestic Violence Workshop, 1996 Oct 24. (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - E.A. Gibson Middle School, 1996 Oct 25. (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Virginia Urban Forest Conference, 1996 Oct 30. (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - NAACP State Conference, 1996 Nov 2. (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Stanley Watts Lecture, 1996 Nov 7. (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - 50th Anniversary of the Hunter Holmes McGuire Veterans Affairs Medical Center, 1996 Nov 8. (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - 7th District Republican Auction, 1996 Nov 9. (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Governor's Commission on Environmental Stewardship, 1996 Nov 12. (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Technology Lunch, 1996 Nov 15. (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Environmental Stewardship Meeting, 1996 Nov 20. (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Shaw Pittman Potts and Trowbridge Attorney Lunch, 1996 Nov 26. (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Farm Bureau Annual Convention, 1996 Dec 5. (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Roanoke Economic Development, 1996 Dec 5. (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Israel Project Interchange, 1996 Dec 7-1996 Dec 16. (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - 1996 Miscellaneous, 1996. (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Commission on Family Violence Prevention, 1997 Jan 6. (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Commonwealth Prayer Breakfast, 1997 Jan 16. (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Associated General Contractors Convention, 1997 Jan 17. (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Virginia Association of Realtors, 1997 Jan 17. (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Mothers Against Drunk Driving Organization, 1997 Jan 18. (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - National Federation of Independent Businesses Day, 1997 Jan 19. (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Concerned Women for America, 1997 Jan 20. (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Association of Virginia Colleges and Universities, 1997 Jan 21. (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Fraternal Order of Police Day, 1997 Jan 22. (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Commonwealth College Day, 1997 Jan 23. (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Washington Post Dinner, 1997 Jan 28. (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - TET '68 Reunion, 1997 Feb 1. (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - 1997 Mid-Session Legislative Reception, 1997 Feb 5. (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Virginia's Congressional Delegation Luncheon, 1997 Feb 10. (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Jewish Community Federation of Richmond, 1997 Feb 10. (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Richmond Academy of Medicine, 1997 Feb 11. (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Blue Ribbon Commission, 1997 Feb 13. (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Chamber of Commerce Lunch, 1997 Feb 14. (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - NAACP Banquet, 1997 Feb 18. (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Financial Executives Institute, 1997 Feb 18. (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Chesapeake Environmental Improvement Council Awards Lunch, 1997 Mar 5. (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - International Association of Financial Planning, 1997 Mar 14. (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Triad Conference, 1997 Mar 17. (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Virginia Chamber Capital Access Summit, 1997 Mar 24. (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Hunton and Williams Lunch, 1997 Mar 27. (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - International Business Lunch, 1997 Mar 28. (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Virginia Environmental Compliance Update, 1997 Apr. (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Virginia Crime Victim Right's Act, 1997 Apr 13. (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Virginia State University, 1997 Apr 16. (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Rotary International Convention, 1997 Apr 17-1997 Apr 19. (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Virginia Horse Festival, 1997 Apr 19. (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Victim's Rights Rededication Service, 1997 Apr 19. (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Chuck Olsen Prison Fellowship Banquet, 1997 Apr 24. (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Shenandoah Apple Blossom Festival, 1997 May 3. (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Associated General Contractors Dinner, 1997 May 13. (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Virginia Coal Council, 1997 May 13. (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Central Business District Association, 1997 May 21. (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Virginia Technology Summit, 1997 May 21. (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Prince William 66, 1997 May 22. (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - Law Enforcement Torch Run Special Olympics, 1997 May 31. (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Attorney General's Summit on Protecting Virginia's Places of Worship from Arson and Vandalism, 1997 July. (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Donation and Gift Form,. (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Regrets, 1994-1997. (Box 4-5)
    - Regrets, 1994. (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - Regrets, 1995. (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Jan 1996 Regrets, 1996 Jan. (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Feb 1996 Regrets, 1996 Feb. (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - March 1996 Regrets, 1996 Mar. (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - April 1996 Regrets, 1996 Apr. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - May 1996 Regrets, 1996 May. (Box 5, Folder 2-3)
    - June 1996 Regrets, 1996 June. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - July 1996 Regrets, 1996 July. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - August 1996 Regrets, 1996 Aug. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - September 1996 Regrets, 1996 Sept. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - October 1996 Regrets, 1996 Oct. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - November 1996 Regrets, 1996 Nov. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - December 1996 Regrets, 1996 Dec. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - January 1997 Regrets, 1997 Jan. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - February 1997 Regrets, 1997 Feb. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - March 1997 Regrets, 1997 Mar. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - April 1997 Regrets, 1997 Apr. (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - May 1997 Regrets, 1997 May. (Box 5, Folder 15-16)
    - June 1997 Regrets, 1997 June. (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - July 1997 Regrets, 1997 July. (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - August 1997 Regrets, 1997 Aug. (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - September 1997 Regrets, 1997 Sept. (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - October 1997 Regrets, 1997 Oct. (Box 5, Folder 21-22)
    - November 1997 Regrets, 1997 Nov. (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - December 1997 Regrets, 1997 Dec. (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - 1998 Regrets, 1997. (Box 5, Folder 25)